-Looks pretty dead.
-Should we just go?
-Didn't book, eh?
-Thought we'd just try our luck.
-Wouldn't recommend it.
Especially not you.
-Okay, yeah, why's that?
-Last group he took out,
there was a young fella --
Looked like you.
College kid.
He was taking a piss off
the side of the boat
and a bull shark jumped up.
Bit his dick off.
- God!
-Well, I don't like
your chances.
Tuck only started
his holidays today,
and he doesn't interrupt
his hols for no one.
Speak of the devil,
here he is.
Milo, shut up!
Mate, you won't need that.
We got some live chum
for you here.
-Ah! Who do we have here, then?
-Greg.
-Tucker. American?
-Canadian.
-Ah, lucky escape.
And this friendly face
belongs to?
-Heather.
-Ah!
Let her answer for herself,
Greg.
-I'm Heather.
-Heather, lovely.
Let me guess -- Pom?
Oh, not bloody s'posed to say
that anymore, are we?
- No, it's fine.
Um, English, yes.
-Mate, I told them
you were on hols, Tuck.
-Ah, so where are you
two lovebirds staying, then?
-Oh, we're not together. Um...
Just --
Just staying at the hostel.
-Okay.
-Sorry we didn't book.
We were supposed to go to
SeaWorld with a bunch of others,
but we slept in.
- It was a big night.
- Yeah, I bet.
- Sorry.
-So, ah...
I guess no one even knows
you guys are here, then.
-Why?
-Well, I just want
to make sure
your last will and testament's
in order.
We will be swimming with sharks,
after all.
- Oh.
- Sweet.
-So, I'm seven years old.
I'm out there
on my boogie board,
splashing around
in the shallows, you know.
Scrawny little arms
and legs kind of flapping away
and swimming out there
and, I don't know,
I guess from underneath
I must have looked like a seal.
Fuckin' boom!
-This bloody white gets me.
-And it just let you go?
-Yeah.
You are looking at a genuine
walking, talking miracle.
-Did it hurt?
-Well, it didn't tickle.
Yeah, it didn't tickle.
Woke me up, though, you know?
I've been wide awake ever since.
-And this was just random?
-I mean, apparently
there was a sign
about a shark sighting
or something, but...
oopsie!
-Wasn't there
someone watching you?
-Well...
Let's just say I used to spend
a lot of time on my own.
-I just can't believe
you do this for a living.
I'd never go near water
again after that.
-It's not the shark's fault.
-You okay?
-Yep.
-It'll be alright.
-It's fine, yeah.
-It's gonna be
a great experience.
-Yeah.
-Alright, crew!
Enough foreplay.
Let's, uh, get you two wet!
-Okay...
-Don't worry, I got you.
Oh, my God, I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
Oh! Oh!
-Oh, it's a mako.
Cheetahs of the sea.
-I can't do it.
I-I can't --
-Well, not yet, you can't.
'Cause there's still one thing
we need to take care of.
Now, listen.
This is a very special
ancient relaxation practice
that, uh, was taught to me
and then it took many years
at sea to master.
If you'll just go with me here,
I promise you it'll help.
Now close your eyes.
Take a big, deep inhale.
And out.
And in.
♪ Baaaaaaaaa... ♪
♪ ...by shark,
doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Baby shark,
-♪ Baby shark, doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo ♪
-Wha...?
- ♪ Baby shark ♪
- No.
-♪ Baby shark ♪
-♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
-It only works
if you sing along.
-I can't!
-♪ Baby shark ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Baby shark... ♪
-Come on, Heather!
-♪ Baby shark ♪
-♪ Here comes Mommy Shark ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Mommy shark,
doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
♪ Mommy Shark and Daddy... ♪
Mm-hmm. Mm.
Oh, my God, that was amazing!
-Shits all over Sea World, eh?
-You can say that again.
-Yeah, something to tell
the grand-kiddies one day.
-Dude. So awesome.
- Yeah.
-Oh, man, thanks so much
for fitting us in --
-Welcome aboard.
-♪ On the floors of Tokyo ♪
♪ Or down in London town
to go, go ♪
♪ With a record selection
and a mirror's reflection ♪
♪ I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪ When there's
no one else in sight ♪
♪ In the crowded lonely night ♪
♪ Well, I wait so long
for my love vibration ♪
♪ And I'm dancing with myself ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh,
dancing with myself ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, dancing
with myself ♪
♪ When there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪ Then I'm dancing
with myself ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ If I looked
all over the world ♪
♪ And there's every type
of girl ♪
♪ But your empty eyes
seem to pass me by ♪
♪ Leave me dancing
with myself ♪
♪ So let's sink another drink ♪
♪ 'Cause it'll give me
time to think ♪
♪ If I had the chance,
I'd ask the world to dance ♪
♪ And I'd be dancing
with myself ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh,
dancing with myself ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, dancing
with myself ♪
♪ When there's nothing to lose
and there's nothing to prove ♪
♪ Then I'm dancing with myself ♪
-Should be there.
Did you look where I said?
-Yeah, I looked.
I can't find the jumper cables.
-Oh. Must be out, then. Sorry.
- Thanks.
Don't s'pose you have any?
-Nah.
What's up?
-Hey, how's it going?
Cracker day out there, eh?
-♪ Well, if I looked
all over the world ♪
♪ And there's every type
of girl ♪
♪ But your empty eyes
seem to pass me by ♪
♪ Leave me dancing with myself ♪
♪ So let's sink another drink ♪
-Hey.
Me again.
-Yeah, dude,
I said I can't help you.
-Ah, you really don't have
jumper cables?
For this?
-What can I say?
I live life on the edge.
-I think the cashier might want
to see that security footage.
-Are you serious?
Is this really what
you're doing?
You're blackmailing me.
-Well, I just need
to get to my car.
I've walked like ten blocks
and I can't find any.
Look, I'm not a serial killer,
okay?
Promise.
Aisle or window?
I have -- I have this theory
that, um, aisle people are
more...open and friendly
whereas, uh, window people
are more, um...
private and thoughtful.
Getting major window vibes.
-Is this a Mormon thing?
'Cause I'm not joining,
so you can save it.
-Why -- Why would you think
I'm a Mormon?
-Dude, you look like you stepped
out of The Book of Mormon.
-Okay, yeah.
No, I'm, uh...
I'm in real estate.
-Great.
-Selling apartments,
not eternal salvation.
-Can you just shut the fuck up?
- Ah, yep.
Yep.
-Nice wheels.
-That was my mum's.
You know,
she gave me a good deal.
-Is that your mom's, too?
-So, where you been surfing?
-Oh, ah, Snapper, mostly.
It's been good.
The peak's a little shifty,
though.
-Yeah.
Do you want to know
a local secret?
-Okay.
-You can't tell a soul, though.
-Window person, remember?
-Yeah. Right.
Okay, well,
next time you paddle out,
you want to look to shore
for the blue bench.
Right, you wanna sit right
in the middle of that bench.
You'll double your wave count.
-Thanks.
-And look, for the record, I...
I never would have narked
about the Slurpee.
-No, yeah, I probably
shouldn't have
judged a book by its cover,
so...we're good.
-Moses Markley.
-Zephyr.
-Nice to meet you, Zephyr.
-Now go start your car.
-Yes, ma'am.
Yes! You're a lifesaver.
-You bet.
-Thank you.
-You a Creedence fan, huh?
-Hell yeah. Are you into 'em?
-Yeah, sure, just not this song.
-What's -- What's wrong with
"Ooby Dooby"?
-Dude, you have "Fortunate Son,"
about poor kids fighting
rich people's wars.
And then you have
"Long As I Can See the Light,
about, like, an outsider
searching to feel understood.
And...
And then you have
"Ooby-fuckin'-Dooby,"
you know,
about some goofy-ass dance.
I just, I don't know.
Yeah, it's a bad song.
Objectively.
-Okay.
The dance is a metaphor.
The song's about love.
-Wow.
It's about that "ooby dooby"
feeling you get in your heart...
-Okay.
-...when you find the one,
and you just gotta go for it.
So what's the alternative?
-♪ Your lips, my lips ♪
♪ Apocalypse ♪
♪ Go and sneak us
through the rivers ♪
-Ow, ow!
-What, what, what, what?
What?
-It's a fin key.
-♪ Come out and haunt me ♪
♪ I know you want me ♪
♪ Come out and haunt me ♪
♪ Sharing all your secrets with
each other since you were kids ♪
-Give me a number.
-No way.
-Oh, come on, I won't judge.
Promise.
-Okay.
Nine.
- Nine! Fuck.
-Oh, fuck off.
You just said no judgment.
-Yeah, but...
nine bread rolls
in one day?
-What can I say?
The waves were all-time,
and bread rolls are cheap.
Not that you have to worry
about that.
- You have deep
psychological issues.
Mm!
- Sorry.
I'm honored
you'd waste one on me.
-It's not wasted.
-Do you know
how many preservatives
are in these things?
-I don't care.
-Mm.
You know I've got
real food inside, right?
Even have running water.
It's kind of a miracle.
-I'm good.
So, what got you into surfing?
-Because...
it's us against the system.
The system
that kills the human spirit.
We stand for something.
To all those dead souls
inching along the freeway
in their metal coffins,
we show them
that the human spirit
is still alive.
-You did not just quote
"Point Break" at me.
-Maybe.
-Mm.
-Mm, but really.
Uh, what got you into surfing?
-Because there was
nothing for me on land.
-♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
-Shit.
Hello?
Anyone here?
Hey, if you can hear me,
I'm just looking for a fin key.
Promise I'll bring it back.
- G'day!
- Jesus!
Yeah, not quite. Tucker.
-Sorry man, I was
just looking for a --
-Fin key.
Yeah, I got you covered.
Let's see what we can do here.
Hey, you're pretty brave,
surfing up here all alone.
That rip can get pretty hectic.
-You're alone, aren't you?
-Touché.
Here ya are.
-Thanks.
I'll bring it right back.
-I got heaps.
-Cool. Appreciate ya.
-♪ Come and see the real thing ♪
♪ Come and see
the real thing ♪
♪ Come and see ♪
♪ I am the real thing ♪
♪ Trying hard
to understand that ♪
♪ Really not, you're seeing me ♪
♪ Trying hard
to understand that... ♪
-Hi.
-What is this?
W-W-Where are we?
-We're on his boat.
-Whose fucking boat?!
-Uh...
-Sorry about the smell.
-Help!
-No one can hear --
Somebody help!
-I've already tried that.
-Help!
-Shit.
-What are you looking for?
-Something
to get these fucking cuffs off.
-You know how to pick a lock?
What do we need?
-Something long and thin,
like a hairpin.
-What is it?
Nothing.
-♪ She came all the way
from America ♪
♪ She had a blind date
with destiny ♪
♪ And the sound
of Te Awamutu... ♪
Mm!
Hey, is there anyone
that'll come looking for you?
Boyfriend or anything?
-There was this guy.
We did the shark dive together.
But...
-What?
-I don't think you wanna know.
Is anyone looking for you?
No.
-♪ Summer's been and gone ♪
♪ Only winter's from now on ♪
-Look, her van was towed.
She wouldn't let that happen,
okay?
It's her home.
Where-- Where's she gonna sleep?
-Look, mate, these transient
types living in their cars...
-She's not like that.
-How long you known this girl?
-I mean --
I mean, it was just...
It was just one night.
Or a day and a night. Uh...
A-A solid 10, 11 hours in total.
But it's not about the quantity,
it's about the quality.
-What was her name?
-Um, Zephyr.
-Last name?
-Um...
-You don't know her last name.
-No, I don't.
-I should have listened.
-My mum didn't want me taking
a gap year.
We had the worst fight about it
before I left.
Now I'm never
going to see her again.
I'm never gonna
see anyone again.
-Why didn't she want
you to take it?
-Because of this.
She was worried it wasn't safe.
You see all these stories on
the news about travelers and...
She also didn't want
me drifting from the plan.
-The plan?
-Law school.
House on the same street.
That sounds like her plan.
It's your life.
You should tell her that
when you see her again.
-Why are you here?
In -- In Australia, I mean.
-To surf.
Get as far away from home
as possible.
-Is your family back in America?
-Which one?
I got a lot of fucking
foster parents to pick from.
-Is that why you know
how to pick a lock?
-What do you mean?
-Like, from juvie or something?
Sorry, I...
I didn't mean to presume.
-No, the only thing
I learned in juvie
is sleep with one eye open,
and a shit ton of bad jokes.
-Can you tell me one?
-Not really in
a joke-telling mood right now.
Just to think about something
else for one second.
Please?
-What do you call the useless
piece of skin on a dick?
-What?
-The man.
That is so true.
Is that an underwire?
-Yeah,
it's cutting the shit out of --
-Give it to me!
-Wait, is this for --
-Yes, yes, the fucking lock!
-Oh!
-Quick!
Sorry, I'm trying.
-Good evening, ladies.
Trust you've had a chance
to get acquainted.
Now, you must be starving.
Oh, not a Vegemite fan?
Well, I s'pose you
wouldn't be the first foreigner
to feel that way, eh?
There you go, just in case.
Water?
Really?
It's a thousand bloody degrees
in here.
Well, please yourself --
-Wait, wait.
-Hang on, what's happened
to your --
-Hey, asshole.
I'm ready for my dinner now.
-Oh, if looks could kill.
Have you ever heard of
the scarlet king snake?
She's a harmless creature,
but quite cleverly mimics
the colorful stripes
of the deadly coral snake.
Now, you're trying hard
to be the coral snake, but...
...we both know that's me.
And you...
Well, you just have
a very pretty pattern.
Mmm.
Tastes like fear.
Hooroo!
-Are you alright?
-Fuck!
-What's going on?
-Hold on, I have to concentrate.
Have you got it?
Almost there.
-Zephyr?
I-I don't feel good.
- No!
No, no!
Oh, you're a fighter.
I love fighters.
Makes for a better show.
What is this?
Why is there a camera?
That's perfect.
Stunning, isn't it?
-What is this?!
What are you doing?!
-You know, most people think
that God is...up here.
Nah.
God's down there.
Where it all started.
Where it all ends.
So, I fish at your beach
and a couple of others, and...
I was really hoping it'd be you.
You know, I see you,
like, come alive on that board.
It's...
...spiritual.
Now, I don't surf,
but I feel the same about...
you know, what I do.
It's...
It's my true calling.
-Don't you fucking touch her!
Hey!
-Heather.
-Huh?
-Hey.
There you are.
-You know why sharks are
more scary than mosquitos,
even though mosquitos kill
a million people each year?
-I don't fucking care!
-It's because people
don't think with their brains.
They think with their guts.
Now, your guts can't understand
mass-murdering insects
and microscopic diseases.
No, what your guts understand...
-...is 300 razor-sharp teeth
and 2,500 pounds of muscle
tearing flesh from bone.
What your guts understand
is the hierarchy
of animals in this world.
-No! No!
Please stop! Stop!
Please stop, please stop!
Please stop!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
-See, the thing about sharks is
they don't actually enjoy
eating people, no.
-I want my Mum!
-She's just a kid...
-When they do attack,
it's unquestionably
a case of mistaken identity.
-You know, you throw chum
overboard day after day
so tourists can get their kicks,
and pretty soon, sharks start
to associate boats with food.
Now, some might argue that this
is a recipe for more accidents,
and, mm, I'm inclined
to agree with him.
-Pull her up! Stop!
Fucking stop!
-No! Pull her up!
Pull her up!
-Just pull her up!
Pull her up, please!
- Fuck yeah.
-Tell me that ain't
the greatest show on Earth.
-Oh, come on,
don't be like that.
I know you ladies don't like
playing second fiddle, but...
it'll be your time
to shine tomorrow night.
-♪ I got some money
in my pocket ♪
♪ I got the car keys
in my hand ♪
♪ I got myself
a couple of tickets ♪
♪ To see
a rock 'n' rollin' band ♪
♪ Come on, girl,
just get on your shoes ♪
♪ We're gonna hear some sounds ♪
♪ Come on, babe, you know there
ain't no time to mess around ♪
♪ Evie ♪
♪ Evie, Evie, Evie,
let your hair hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie ♪
♪ Let your hair hang down ♪
♪ You got the body of a woman ♪
♪ The way you move it
like a queen ♪
-♪ Come on, babe, you know there
ain't no time to mess around ♪
♪ Evie, Evie, Evie,
let your hair hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie ♪
♪ Evie, let your hair
hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie, Evie,
let your hair hang down ♪
♪ Evie, Evie ♪
♪ Let your hair hang down ♪
-♪ So, won't you try it, baby ♪
♪ I'll take you by the hand ♪
Fuck!
-May I?
Ah, come on, I know
what you're thinking, but...
a joke's only funny once.
Hey, listen,
you've lost a lot of fluid
and you know, you're gonna
need your strength later.
Where's that fight
I saw in you, huh?
-Get away from me,
you twisted fuck.
-Do you understand
what happens to the ecosystem
if you remove the shark?
Ah, their -- their prey operates
without constraint.
But the shark...
The shark brings order.
And without this...
chaos reigns and...
...well, weaker
creatures just...
think they can do
whatever they want.
- Jesus.
Give me a fucking break.
I've never met anyone
who likes the sound
of their voice so much.
Don't compare yourself
to the shark.
They're highly evolved.
You're just a pathetic coward
who kills women
because Mommy never loved you,
or whatever.
You are the lowest of the low.
A worm.
Even lower than a worm.
You are the toxic fucking trash
that floats in the ocean.
-Hm.
I notice you haven't used
the facilities yet.
You might want to consider that.
You know, things can tend
to get a little...
undignified.
-No! Pull her up, pull her up!
Please, please, pull her up!
Come on...
Hello? Hello?
Help! I need help!
Help! Help!
-Well, at least someone's having
a good time, eh?
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah.
Hey, be careful with that.
Hey, you fuckin' put that down.
-You put that down
or you won't even make it
to the fucking hook.
Ah!
Aah!
-We're looking for a blonde
female Caucasian...
- Hey!
-Hey, Milo, shut up!
Hey, Tucky!
Mate, I thought
you were gone all week.
-I gotta get some supplies.
-That's not like you to run out.
-First time for everything.
-Mate, I got something for ya.
Mate, will you stop?
I got something good for us.
Yesterday,
some rich wanker, right,
pulls up
with his rich wanker kid
on a rich wanker boat.
But it was nice, mate.
They want to go diving.
I tell them the Tuck's on hols,
mate.
But now since you're back,
maybe we can catch them
before they go, mate.
I got their number
just in case, if...
It's on one of these.
Alright, I reckon there's gonna
be a nice tip in this for you
and maybe there's just
a little finder's fee
for the old Daveroo, mate.
-Ahoy there!
Tucker's Shark Experience
is currently closed
while your captain takes
a well-earned holiday.
Please call back after the 13th
and I'll introduce you
to the most misunderstood
creatures on Earth.
-Uh, hi. Um...
I'm not exactly sure
what I'm asking for,
but, uh, just give me
a call back, please.
Thanks.
-Can you fucking move?
What?
-Fuck. Fuck.
Hey, hey, hey.
-Thank you.
You gotta go...
go find a paperclip or a skewer
or fucking something
to pick the locks with.
I'll talk you through it.
Quick, before he comes back.
Go! And call the cops!
-Police, fire, or ambulance?
-Hello? Police,
fire, or ambulance?
Poli--
-Sorry, I can't hear you.
Could you repeat that?
-Help!
Aah!
-Sir, if you need assistance
but you're unable to speak,
please press --
-Where the fuck
did you come from?
-Tuck, are you --
Are you alright, mate?
-Hello?!
-Moses?
-Please!
-Hello?
Jesus, what...
-Help!
Mate, have you got a sheila
down there I don't know about?
Fuck, Tuck!
-Oh, God.
What did you do to him?
Moses! Moses!
-Zeph.
-I'm right here.
-I have fucked up the rescue.
-You almost stuck it.
-Hm.
Some hero I turned out to be.
-Coming to find me
is hero enough.
Don't suppose you got through
to the cops?
-I didn't get to say
where we were.
Why are we stopping?
-That bad, huh?
Why'd you do a runner
that morning?
-I told you.
Early bird gets the barrel.
-Bullshit.
Tell me you didn't feel it.
-I'm just better off alone.
-No one's better off alone.
That's just something
people say.
-No. It's not.
You don't know me.
You don't --
-I know you.
I know you dig Creedence.
I know you're...
in the Guinness Book of Records
for the most bread rolls
consumed in one day.
-I know you're tough.
And I know you're really warm.
And funny.
I know...
No, I sense...
...that you haven't had
as much kindness
in your life as you deserve.
-Stop.
-That's why you ran.
-Because...
...it's hard to trust when...
...all you know is
why you shouldn't.
-M-Moses, I really don't have
the strength for this right now.
No, you can't!
-I've decided to add a matinee.
-Holy fuck.
Who the fuck is that?!
-No!
-Aah! Ah!
-Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
No, he's not a tourist.
He drives his Mom's Volvo,
for fuck's sake.
He has money. Think about it.
They're never gonna
stop looking for him.
Don't be fucking stupid.
No!
-Moses!
-Help!
-Aah!
-Fucking help!
-No!
- Fuck!
-Wait!
-Put me up instead.
-Zeph, no!
-Please!
H-He doesn't deserve this!
Aw, how romantic.
It's too bad
I'm more of a horror fan.
-Fuck! Fuck!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stop! Fuck!
-Fuck!
Don't you fucking move!
Be as still as you possibly can.
-That's a bull shark.
Most culled shark in the ocean.
Serious anger issues.
No!
-Fuck you!
-Well, that oughta
ring the dinner bell.
Fuck!
- Please,
don't do this.
-Fuck yeah.
Brief intermission,
ladies and gentlemen.
-Moses?
-Where's that fuckin' chopper?
Keep going.
Keep going. Keep going.
Fuck!
Ugh...
-Guessing he's not hungry.
Look, if it's
any consolation, you...
You weren't right
for each other.
You know, he's soft and...gooey.
And you're hard.
You're hard as nails.
Like me.
-I'm nothing like you.
-Yeah, you are.
Yeah, you and me...
...we're sharks.
Solitary creatures.
We fend for ourselves.
Yeah, I've got a feeling that
tonight's show is gonna be
fuckin' one for the ages.
Fuck.
It's probably a good thing
you can't see this.
-♪ Mommy Shark ♪
♪ Mommy Shark ♪
Oh, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, fuck, fuck,
fuck, fuck, fuck.
No. Fuck!
Oh!
Help!
-♪ For you are mine
at last ♪
♪ For you are mine ♪
♪ At last ♪
Zeph.
-Oh, mate, you think
you don't want to watch...
But deep down...you do.
That's the thing
about us men, man.
We don't really know
what's inside until it pops out.
And once that happens, there's
really no stuffing it back in.
-Now, can either of you tell me
why the marlin is the sports
fisherman's fish of choice?
Anyone? I'll give you a hint.
It's not because of her size
and it's not
because of her beauty.
It's because of her...fight!
See, every fisherman loves
a good fight.
And you'll get a marlin
and you'll fuckin'
bring her right in there
and you'll get her right up
to the boat
and you'll think you've got her
and then fuckin' -- zzzz! --
she makes another run for it
and it's fucking exhilarating,
man.
You know?
But the thing
the fish doesn't realize
is that once that hook sets,
no matter how hard she runs,
doesn't matter how many times...
she's already in the boat.
And the game's rigged, you know?
'Cause it's life and death
for the fish.
But for the fishermen,
it's just an afternoon
of good old-fashioned fun.
Fun can't last forever,
though, can it?
No, no.
No, sooner or later,
the marlin must meet her fate.
- Oh!
-Oh, I'd hoped this would be
one for the ages.
I was right.
Fuck, she's gonna turn
those little arms and legs
into toothpicks.
Right! Places, please!
And...
action!
-Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck, be calm.
Be calm.
-Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop!
-Oi! Get!
Go on, get!
It's not your night.
-Where are ya?
I know you're there, babe,
or the bull wouldn't have left.
-You just won't quit,
will you, marlin?
-Behind you!
- Boo!
- Aah!
-Where are you, marlin?
-Ooby dooby, motherfucker.
Aah!
-Zeph!
Zeph!
Moses? Hey.
Moses!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Moses, wake up. Wake up.
Moses, please wake up.
Hey.
Help!
Help! Help!
Moses!
Hey, hey, Mo, wake up.
Moses, wake up.
Help is on the way.
Hey. Please wake up.
Please. Hey.
Hey, hey. Moses.
Hey, I want to tell
you something.
When I said there's nothing
for me on land?
There's you. Okay?
Please wake up.
Oh, my God.
-I knew it.
-♪ Hey, baby,
when you jump over here ♪
♪ When you do the ooby-dooby
I want to be near ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Well, you wiggle to the left,
wiggle to the right ♪
♪ Do the ooby-dooby
with all of your might ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah ♪
♪ Well, you wiggle and you shake
like a big rattle snake ♪
♪ You do the ooby-dooby till
you think your heart'll break ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-ah ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah-ah ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Well, you'll be struttin'
'cause now you know ♪
♪ How to do the ooby-dooby,
now baby let's go! ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah ♪
♪ Hey, baby, jump over here ♪
♪ When you do the ooby-dooby
I gotta be near ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby,
ooby-dooby, ooby-dooby ♪
♪ Do-wah-do-wah-do-wah ♪
-♪ Don't walk up
close behind her ♪
♪ Don't whisper in her ear ♪
♪ Don't think you can
outsmart her ♪
♪ For soon you'll disappear ♪
♪ Be careful what you wish for ♪
♪ Little fishies that you took ♪
♪ There's blood
all in the water ♪
♪ And you just got the hook ♪
♪ No man will ever own her ♪
♪ She's dangerous ♪
♪ The queen below the water ♪
♪ Don't ever swim above her ♪
♪ She's dangerous ♪
♪ Don't say I didn't warn ya ♪
♪ Don't tread
where you not oughta ♪
♪ Don't curse away the sun ♪
♪ Don't play the game
that brought ya ♪
♪ The sickness on the rain ♪
♪ Don't sleep
without the darkness ♪
♪ Don't dream
without the light ♪
♪ The twisted mind inside ya ♪
♪ Is bound to feel the bite ♪
♪ No man will ever own her ♪
♪ She's dangerous ♪
♪ The queen below the water ♪
♪ Don't ever swim above her ♪
♪ She's dangerous ♪
♪ Don't say I didn't warn ya ♪
♪ No man will ever own her ♪
♪ She's dangerous ♪
♪ The queen below the water ♪
♪ Don't ever swim above her ♪
♪ She's dangerous ♪
♪ Don't say I didn't warn ya ♪